<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shuo Yan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shuo Yan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My progress on STAT385</title>
      <link>/blog/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 16:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/third/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently taking STAT385: Statistics Programming Methods
We talked about some basic R data types, control flow, loops as well as plotting!
The current project it to build a personal project, which is this one!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Shuo Yan. I am a student in University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign with a double major of psychology and statistics.
My interest lies in clinical psychology. My career goal is to be a psychiatrist or a conselor. I also have strong passions in math and statistics.
I am currently a research assistent in BEAST Lab which focuses on how emotion affects reasoning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beast Lab</title>
      <link>/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 15:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>Beast Lab is a lab in Psychology Department of Univerisity of Illinois. We focus on psychopathology studies.
A project we are working on is about how mental disorders affect reasoning. Our hypothesis is that people with depression will selectively inhibit infomation received. During experiment, we record how people with depression may take different response time to information provided for analogies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 15:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Please have a look of my Resume
Or download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>handwriting recognizer</title>
      <link>/blog/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 16:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/second/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this handwriting recognizer which recognizes handwriting dragged on the laptop touch bar.
To use it, simply drag a letter on your touch bar and the program tells you what you&amp;rsquo;ve just written.
It&amp;rsquo;s based on naive bayes algorithm. If you are interested, please check out handwriting recognizer</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>